Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series IV. Alumni and Students
  - Dr. Isidor I and Mrs. Sylvia Sprecher standing beside Dr. Sprecher's 1939 Cornell DVM diploma, early 1990s, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    Item number: 1939
  - Roy C. Johnston, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
    Item number: negative
  - Florence Kimball 1910 class photo, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - John D. Murray at lectern, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - James and Linda Dixon Reeve Peddie, class of 1965, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
    Item number: 1965
  - Patricia O'Connor Halloran, Class of 1939 at Staten Island Zoo's dinner in her honor October 25, 1999 with Dean Donald F Smith, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Claude Rosenthal presenting diploma of Jerome Rosenthal '02 to Dean Donald Smith at scholarship reception April 16, 2004, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
    Item number: 1902
  - Claude Rosenthal with Stephen Ettinger and Dean Donald Smith holding diploma of Jerome Rosenthal '02 at scholarship reception April 16, 2004, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Harold M. Zweighaft '56 with Salmon Alumni Award medal, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    Item number: 1956
  - John D. McAuliff '18 portrait from 1961 Practitioner Research Award, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Alphi Psi - group of members, Undated (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - Class composite, 1973
  - Class composite, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Class composite, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Class composite, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Class composite, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Class composite, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Class composite, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Class composite, 2017 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Hillary Clinton at podium (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Series V. Buildings and Facilities
  - General (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Lower Campus - General (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1900 Fire-Histology Department Losses (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Upper Campus-General (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Upper Campus-Group III Equipment Estimates-F1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Upper Camps-Group III Equipment Estimates-F2, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Upper Camps-Group III Equipment Estimates-F3, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Upper Campus-Group III Equipment Estimates-F4, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Upper Campus-Group IV Equipment Estimates, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Upper Campus-Space Requirements, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Research Tower, General (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Research Tower-Ulrich Franzen and Associated Material, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Research Tower-Earl L. Walls Associates Material, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Research Tower-Dedication, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Physical Biology Computer Facility-Proposal, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Veterinary Medical Center (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Facility Master Plan by Davis, Brody and Associates-Folder 1, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Facility Master Plan by Davis, Brody and Associates-Folder 2, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Space Allocation by Department, Davis, Brody etc., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Building Plans (Box 9)
  - Photographs
  - Aerial Views of Buildings - slides, 1959-1990s (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Various Buildings - slides, 1903-2002 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Various Buildings - some slides, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Computer Labs, no date (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Learning Lab, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Facilities Off Campus - slides, 1983-2003 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Labs - some slides, 1974-2001 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Lunging Arena, no date (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Modular Resource Center - slides, 1990s-2002 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Mouse House Dedication, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Muenscher Poisonous Plant Garden - slides, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Research Tower, 1970s (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Research Tower Fire - slides, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Veterinary Medical Center Dedication, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Veterinary Medical Center Dedication - Design and Planning, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Vet College Photography, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Wet Lab, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Aerial view of James Law Hall, Moore Lab, etc. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings and James Law Hall (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Clinic buildings in James Law Hall (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Architect's sketch of Moore Laboratory Building (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Front of Moore Laboratory with 4 cars (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - View of museum floor with display cases in James Law Hall (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Empty pathology and bacteriology laboratory -- in James Law Hall; no students (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Empty pathology and bacteriology laboratory -- in James Law Hall with a fume hood in the ceiling; no students (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Diagram of library stack level in Schurman Hall, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sketch of Veterinary Research Tower, 2000? (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sketch of Veterinary Medical Center, 2000? (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Aerial photos of Veterinary Complex about 1957; cars in crescent shaped parking lot., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - View of Schurman Hall and Small Animal Clinic, about 1957., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Aerial view of Veterinary Complex, about 1957; No cars in crescent shaped parking lot., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Folder of Schurman Hall building diagrams by floor and area., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - NYS College of Agriculture barns with large Elm tree on right, 1913? (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Dark colored gabled barn with 2 extensions; 2 round silos on left., 1913? (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Several dark colored barns, 1913 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - View over Libe Slope toward West Campus in spring (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Clinic and hospital building, New York State Veterinary College, Cornell University -architects drawing, 1913 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinics buildings viewed from east, 1913 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings viewed from southeast with grass in right corner, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings viewed from southeast with road in foreground, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Small Animal Clinic and large electrical pole and Roberts Hall in background, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Small Animal Clinic with trees in winter, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Small Animal and Large Animal Clinics with roof, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Small Animal and Large Animal Clinics with telephone pole without roof, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Medical clinic with two black cars for ambulatory service and farriery on right, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Medical large animal clinic, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Medical large animal clinic - positive, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Farriery from southwest, Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - road on north side of Small Animal Clinic [today's Tower Road], 1920 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - area between medical clinics, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings from east with Barton Hall, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - farriery from southwest, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings - Old clinic used as postmorten room, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic building - farriery from southeast with grass, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Clinic building - from east with Barton Hall, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Fire damage to 2nd floor south of James Law Hall, 1900-11-13 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 44533
  - Law Hall with stripped flag on top of building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421
  - Law Hall with flag from printed page labeled "Main Building", Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall with flag (same as from printed page), Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall with flag on top of building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.11
  - Law Hall with flag and long driveway, 1904 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall no flag with shubbery in front, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.12
  - Law Hall with no flag on top of building, 1904 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.2
  - Law Hall from northwest in summer, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.3
  - Law Hall with tropical garden pond in front, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.31
  - Law Hall with south wing and 3 black cars, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.4
  - Law Hall double entrance doors, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 422.41
  - Law Hall from northwest closer in, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.42
  - Law Hall with 7 black automobiles, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.7
  - Law Hall toward south side, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.41
  - Law Hall toward front, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall with large tree in right front and medical clinic building in rear, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.5
  - Law Hall with very large tree in right front, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.6
  - Law Hall surrounded by trees, 1957-10-31 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.8
  - Law Hall side entrance covered by ivy, 1957-10-31 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.87
  - Law Hall from rear with meadow, 1905 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.813
  - Law Hall walkway on north side, 1957-10-31 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 421.82
  - Law Hall with Medical Clinic in rear, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall with no flag, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall and outbuilding, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall driveway to Med Clinic, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 278
  - Law Hall from rear showing two wings, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: 10-317-83
  - Law Hall from front in color, Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall from postcard "Cornell Veterinary College, Ithaca, N.Y.", Undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Item number: CN3-99-86
  - Law Hall south win with one black automobile, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall with south wing and medical clinic, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall southwest corner with man in dark coat, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall with lawn med clinics and autos, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall southwest corner with 2 men and autos, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall front in spring, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall southside with south wing, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall from southwest with many autos and rock in driveway, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall south wing med clinic and long drive A, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall south wing med clinic and long drive B, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall south wing med clinic and long drive C, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Law Hall south wing no autombiles, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Moore Lab and Law Hall, 1944-05 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Moore Lab - Entrance doors with cow pediment, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Item number: 3-148-86
  - Moore Lab - Entrance door pediment only, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Item number: 514/92
  - Moore Lab - Front showing double entrance - postive, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Moore Lab - Architect drawing, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Moore Lab - showing Barton Hall on right, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Item number: 422.1
  - Moore Lab - Back of building in snow with two cars, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Item number: 10-318-83
  - Moore Lab - Outside from southeast showing entrance, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Item number: 422.2
  - Moore Lab and Law Hall in spring with person in crosswalk, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Item number: 420.2
  - Moore Lab and Law Hall in spring with person in doorway, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Item number: 420.1
  - Moore Lab and Law Hall in winter snow, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Moore Lab with man and woman moving from Law Hall toward two-tone Rolls Royce car with licence tag Hooper, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Moore Lab - Rolls Royce car with licence marker Hooper parked between Moore Lab and Law Hall, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Morrill Hall seen looking west, Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Item number: APC 353
  - Dairy Building (later became part of Goldwin Smith Hall, Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Entrance to Chemical Engineering Building in winter with snow, Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Groom cottage on Veterinary Campus next to James Law Hall (seen in background), Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Item number: 429
  - Panorama of Cornell campus, Undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Veterinary College Complex with tennis court from Sage Hall, 1900 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Item number: 420
  - Veterinary College Complex with observatory from Sage Hall, 1905 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Veterinary College complex with Roberts Hall observatory and field in back, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Item number: 420.6
  - Veterinary College complex, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Vet College Complex with house in foreground and Roberts Hall in back, 1923 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Veterinary College Complex with Barton Hall and Agric Buildings, Undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Item number: 2582
  - Veterinary College Complex, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Item number: 7-193-93
  - Cornell campus with Vet College in upper right, Undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Moore Lab with Law Hall and Clinics, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - McGraw clock tower, negative, Undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Fireplace with lounge chairs showing the andirons produced by farrier Henry Asmus in the seminar room in Moore Laboratory, constructed in 1938, 1938 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Item number: 432
  - Table with teaching elements practice models in forge room of Farriery Building, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Item number: 437
  - Closeup of forge room with tables and hoods in Farriery Building, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Item number: 437.1
  - Forge room with hoods and ducts in Farriery Building, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Item number: 437.2
  - Anatomy laboratory in James Law Hall, Undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Chemistry laboratory in Moore Laboratory??, Undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Item number: 432.3
  - Materia medica and pharmacy lab in Law Hall??, Undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Item number: 435
  - Medical (clinical pathology) lab in James Law Hall??, Undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Item number: 436.4
  - Research lab in Moore Laboratory building, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Item number: 432.5
  - Research lab in Moore Laboratory building, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Item number: 432.51
  - Pathology and bacteriology lab on third floor of James Law Hall, Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Pathology and bacteriology lab on third floor of James Law Hall, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 431.51
  - Sterilizing autoclav with refregerator in bacteriology in Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 432.22
  - Sterilizing autoclav closeup in bacteriology in Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 432.23
  - Pathology lab tables on third floor of James Law Hall, Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 431.42
  - Bacteriology lab tables in Moore Laboratory, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 432.21
  - Bacteriology lab tables closeup in Moore Laboratory, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 432.2
  - Pathology student lab in Moore Laboratory, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 432.41
  - Pathology student lab in Moore Laboratory, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 432.42
  - Pathology student lab in Moore Laboratory, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 432.43
  - Pathology student lab in Moore Laboratory, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    Item number: 432.4
  - Physiology lab of Dr. PA Fish on 2nd floor north of James Law Hall, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Item number: 431.41
  - Physiology lab on second floor in James Law Hall, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Item number: 431.4
  - Physiology lab on second floor of James Law Hall, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Physiology apparatus for basel metabolism, Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Item number: 431.43
  - Physiology apparatus for basel metabolism, Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Item number: 431.44
  - Amphitheater in south wing of James Law Hall, taken by Troy Studio, 1929, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Amphitheater in south wing of James Law Hall showing head of the Auzouz papier-mache horse model, Undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Tiered lecture room in the Medical Building used for clinical instruction, Undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Item number: 436
  - Lecture Room #101 in Moore Laboratory, used from 1938 to 1957, Undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Item number: 432.12
  - Small microbiology and pathology lecture room on second floor of James Law Hall, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Small lecture room (with armed captain chairs) on second floor of James Law Hall that later became Dr. Gilman's laboratory, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Item number: 431.22
  - Lecture room from back in north wing of James Law Hall, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Item number: 431.2
  - Anatomy lecture room on second floor of James Law Hall, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Item number: 431.31
  - Medical clinic passageway with sink on right in the Medical Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Item number: 436.1
  - Medical clinic room with sink on left in the Medical Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Item number: 436.11
  - Medical clinic isolation stalls for horses in the Medical Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Item number: 436.3
  - Medical clinic stanchion for examining large animals in the Medical Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Item number: 433.1
  - Medical clinic cattle and horse ward in the Medical Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Waiting room with table chairs sink in the Small Animal Clinic building, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    Item number: 430.1
  - General ward of the Small Animal Clinic building, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    Item number: 430.4
  - Isolation ward with bathtub of the Small Animal Clinic building, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    Item number: 435.2
  - General ward of the Small Animal Clinic building, 1914 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    Item number: 435.3
  - Waiting room with chairs around periphery of the Small Animal Clinic, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Item number: UP-4599-J
  - Examination room with one table, cabinet and sink in the Small Animal Clinic, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Item number: UP-4599-F
  - Examination room with two tables, sink and scales in the Small Animal Clinic, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Item number: UP-4599-A
  - Surgery with two operatingroom tables in the Small Animal Clinic, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Item number: UP-4599-G
  - Kennel room for cats in the Small Animal Clinic, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Item number: UP-4599-I
  - Kennel room for dogs in the Small Animal Clinic, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Item number: UP-4599-B
  - Pathology museum on third floor of James Law Hall, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Anatomy museum looking south on first floor of James Law Hall, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    Item number: 431.6
  - Poultry necropsy room with dissecting table in Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Hydraulic lift necropsy table for large animals in mid level position in Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Hydraulic lift necropsy table for large animals at floor level in Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Hydralic lift necropsy table for large animals at mid level with overhead electric hoist in Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Refrigerator room for large animals in necropsy suite in Moore Laboratory, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Staff office in Moore Laboratory Building, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Item number: 432.1
  - Staff office in Moore Laboratory Building, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Item number: 432.11
  - Unidentified room in Medical Clinic Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Item number: 430.3
  - Large animal surgery operating room with large flat table in Medical Clinic Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
    Item number: 436.2
  - Angle view of operating table for large animals in the Medical Building, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    Item number: 433
  - Front view of operating table with letter labels for large animals in the Medical Building, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    Item number: 438.1
  - Small animal surgery operating room with tilted table in the Small Animal Clinic Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
    Item number: 435.11
  - Small animal surgery operating room with angled table in the Small Animal Clinic Building, Undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
    Item number: 435.1
  - Library alumni periodical room no journal issues on empty reading tables, 1915 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    Item number: 431.731
  - Library alumni periodical room with journal issues on reading tables, 1915 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Library brass door plaque, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
    Item number: 4-452-88
  - Library office doorway in James Law Hall, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
    Item number: 431.715
  - Library office with librarian at desk with shelves behind, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
    Item number: 431.761
  - Library office with librarian at desk near window, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
    Item number: 431.76
  - Library Alumni Room with decorations for student-faculty part made by Rebecca Gifford '40, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
    Item number: 431.77
  - Library Alumni Room with table and lamp, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
    Item number: 431.771
  - Two veterinary students in library - Nugent and Ruben Gordon A, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Two veterinary students in library - Nugent and Ruben Gordon B, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Library workroom door seen after Law and Moore portraits were hung in the reading room, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
    Item number: 431.71
  - Library portrait of standing Dean Veranus Moore and card catalog A, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Library portrait of standing Dean Veranus Moore and card catalog B, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Library reading room card catalog on right, doorway in center, Undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.711
  - Library reading room with 3 men in white lab coats reading; one is Dr. Frank Hare as graduate student, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.74
  - Library reading room with empty tables some books, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 731.711.1
  - Library reading room with windows and empty desk, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.712
  - Library reading room with 1 female student in plaid shirt reading, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.713
  - Library reading room with 1 female student in dark cardigan reading from side, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.714
  - Library reading room empty with James Law portrait on wall, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.72
  - Library reading room with 1 female student in dark cardigan reading from front, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.721
  - Library reading room with 1 male student reading near window, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.722
  - Library reading room with librarian seated at reference desk in front of bookcases, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.742
  - Library reading room with 1 female student in plaid shirt reading, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.743
  - Library reading room with 4 men in white coats reading: Alex Gow '29, Dr. Bennett, Donald Baker '29, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Item number: 431.723